<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ryuichiro Suzuki</title>
    <link>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ryuichiro Suzuki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 15:41:36 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpine Ruby Nokogiri Issue</title>
      <link>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/posts/alpine-ruby-nokogiri-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 15:41:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/posts/alpine-ruby-nokogiri-issue/</guid>
      <description>The issue I was doing practice of Github workflow by making a basic task app using Rails
I was using
ruby:3.1.2-alpine3.14 (for the base image) Rails 7.0.4 Initially, everything was going smoothly but once I shut down the computer one day and came to work on it again, I started getting error from Nokogiri every time I try to bundle install in the container.
Gem::Ext::BuildError: ERROR: Failed to build gem native extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/projects/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 19:50:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/projects/test/</guid>
      <description>hello hihihihi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 15:23:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/resume/</guid>
      <description>Work Experience OpenSalary June 2022 - Present Full stack software engineer OpenSalary is a web site that provides free and open information about salaries of those who work in the Japanese tech industry. OpenSalary is a community driven platform made by developers, for the benefit of developers. We aim to empower software engineers with the data they need to make informed career decisions.
I joined the team to speed up the development of the website and make the product more valuable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi. I&#39;m Scooter</title>
      <link>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 15:04:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://effulgent-belekoy-b37d9e.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>TLDR I am a full-stack web developer and very passionate about technology and computer science. I am an alumni of Le Wagon Tokyo, a coding bootcamp founded in France. Since graduation, I worked in three different companies as a freelance full stack developer, while teaching programming at the bootcamp I graduated from. I am a Japanese / English bilingual 🇯🇵🇬🇧
Long version Where am I from? I was born in Tokyo Japan, and grew up there until 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
